Percival is a young boy who
lived with his grandfather
in a remote place called Finger of God.
Those happy days came to an end by the
sudden appearance of his father, Ironside.
Percival set out on a journey with the
thoughts of his lost grandfather in mind.
Along the way, he learned about the prophecy
of the Four Knights of the Apocalypse,
and that he is one of the knights prophesied to destroy the world.
He then learned that following
his fate will lead him
to the enemy that killed
his grandfather, Ironside.
Percival grew through encounters with his
friends and battles with his pursuers,
and eventually arrived
at the Kingdom of Liones.
Where he met King Meliodas and the Four Knights
of the Apocalypse other than himself.
But the hands of the enemy
reached there as well,
and finally the master of Ironside,
the one who sent many pursuers
after the Knights of Prophecy...
Arthur Pendragon has appeared.
The Four Knights of the Apocalypse are
the ones who will destroy the world.
Percival's destiny is about to take a big turn.
People of Liones.
The Power of the King
Lend an ear to my words.
I am Arthur Pendragon.
I reign over Camelot, to the south,
a land destroyed in the so called "Holy War"
between the Demon King and
the Seven Deadly Sins.
His words are echoing in my mind.
And now you, People of Liones,
have come to the same crossroads
that Camelot once faced.
Destruction... or survival?
The peace you currently possess
is nothing but a stopgap.
The history of Britannia
makes that crystal clear.
The holy war of 3000 years ago,
the one of 16 years ago...
The endless, bloody struggle
between so many races...
And every time, humanity has made
sacrifices for the sake of other species.
I know there are those among you who
lost family or friends in the Holy War...
Who still bear the scars in your hearts.
Scars that not even 16 years can easily heal.
Mom... Dad...
My sister died protecting me
from a demon attack.
Once someone is lost,
they may never return.
The scars etched into the survivors' hearts
will torment them their whole lives.
So what are you getting at?!
We still gotta keep on living
for those we lost!
But what if you could see the family
you love so much again?
If you could express the feelings that you could
never share with your true love before they died?
What if you could make
impossible wishes come true?
That'll never happen!
Do you think we're all stupid?!
You swindler!
No.
Such things do very much exist.
A land where no one hurts,
and no one is forlorn.
A restful place, where everyone is safe
from all threats and disasters.
That is Camelot, my eternal kingdom.
Is this a dream?
My wife! I see her!
If I come to Camelot, will I truly...
Will I ever see my child again?!
Grampa?
My mission in life is to save humanity.
I won't force you, of course,
but please give it some serious thought.
The Seven Deadly Sins truly are the heroes of  kingdom...
but still a motley crowd of different races.
It's plain as day that they will betray
humanity... and all of you.
You're a Knight of Prophecy indeed!
Resisting my "Power of the King"
to launch an attack...
All those deceitful words...
They make me sick.
Ah, youth.
Full
Counter
Well, well, well...
Look at me, crossing swords
with you like this.
My liege!
Fwah!
His liege?
That little dude?
Sorry, but my decision is that...
If mankind wishes to obtain true peace,
they must drive out all non-humans.
Meliodas...
Remember what you told me?
You said that once a man makes
a promise, he shouldn't break it.
But I also said...
Even if you venture down the wrong path,
the Seven Deadly Sins will always follow behind.
Arthur!
It's time to open your eyes!
"Open my eyes," you say?
My eyes are already wide open, and that's
why I stand here, confronting you.
The idea of humans living alongside
other races is nothing but a fantasy,
and I promise you, I'll return this
world back into human hands!
Why did you butt in?!
I-I can handle him myself!
Stand back, Tristan.
I-It blew the mountain away!
Oh, man, what a disaster!
We mustn't meddle in His Majesty's battle!
We need to leave, too!
Wait, Dr. Hendy! Prince Tristan is...
Prince Tristan!
Stay back!
Shut up!
What a naughty child.
A son should never speak to
his kindly father like that.
Trillion Dark
This force...
A darkness great enough
to have physical mass?!
King Arthur!
No! You don't stand a chance.
Are you hurt?
Who asked you for help?!
When are you going to stop
treating me like a child?!
You can't turn back, can you?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I can fight just fine without your help!
You truly are a child.
You understand nothing at all.
What did you...?!
You're just dragging your
father down in this fight.
Don't worry about it.
But I can't say you're much smarter, Meliodas.
Worrying about your son when the fate
of your entire kingdom is at stake.
How could I even serve as a king
if I didn't care about my son?
Then you are no king.
Think, what two things must
the leader of a nation do?
He must decide, and he must act.
To protect his nation and people,
he must abandon himself, his emotions...
Tristan!
And even his own beloved wife and son.
Would you not agree?
Not one bit!
Is that so?
Are you in pain?! Just hold on!
Then you shall die protecting
your precious boy.
No!
Meliodas!
Well, you're wrong.
What?
Tristan!
You're a real handful, you know that?
Shining Road
Hang in there, Tristan!
I...
You've done enough.
One hit tamed that prince's wild side?
Dang!
You guys called him here?!
Duh! It was the fastest way.
So, you did this?
You are another one of the
Four Knights of the Apocalypse, yes?
Are you King Arthur?
What if I am?
Lancelot's strong, but he can't take him.
A one-on-one duel is bad news!
He's so dead.
The fool can't even see when he's outclassed.
Hey, don't say stuff like this.
Hey, uncle, leave this to me, okay?
You got it, Lancelot!
Lancelot?
Don't bother trying to remember my name.
Now that I know you're King Arthur,
that's all that matters.
We haven't met, have we?
Have I done something to earn your wrath?
That sword... nice magic tool.
No matter how many times the blade
snaps, a new one will replace it.
It is Carnwenhan, my chopping
weapon of divine chaos.
What about these choppers?
At last, some entertainment.
Using Chaos power to regenerate?
Why bother using an artificial arm, then?
Your cat monster ate it during
the last holy war, didn't it?
You knew about that, kid?
Well, yes. I was young then.
I keep it as a stern reminder of
my weakness and my naivete.
Sure, whatever.
Just don't use it as an excuse
when you lose, okay?
Ah, youth...
So ignorant, cruel, and sweet.
Man, what are you going on about?
No way!
Wh-Wh-Wha-Wha?!
He's at least an even match for King Arthur!
He's so strong!
Of course, Percival.
His power is far beyond even mine.
Six years ago, Lancelot disappeared from the Kingdom of Benwick,
but reappeared three years later, as if nothing had happened.
He gained fearsome new strength and magic.
He's never even attempted
to explain how or why,
but his current strength could match
the legendary Seven Deadly Sins.
So? Gonna use your right hand now?
Just gonna borrow this for a sec.
Shining Road
There goes another one.
You have quite a gift,
but you still lack the power to defeat me.
Stop it!
Arthur... Wasn't that right arm supposed to be
a reminder of your naivete and weakness?
You can hardly blame me.
You see, Chaos was merely acting
on instinct to protect its vessel.
In other words, it has nothing
to do with my intentions.
That's why not even Lancelot
can read its moves.
I knew I should have wrested you away from Chaos 16 years ago.
Is this even real?
Are we dreaming it all?!
That can't be true.
Finally taking this seriously, huh?
Oh! You're alive!
Do you now see the gap in our strength?
Just so you know.
You're the one who doesn't "see" it.
Huh?!
Such magic pressure...
Wait, wasn't Lancelot left-handed?!
This is your chance to beat him!
O-Oh, my...
L-Look up at the sky!
A monster?!
No! It's a huge flying ship!
Could they be?
Yes... That's them, all right.
The Chaos Knights of Camelot!
Ironside!
My liege, playtime has gone on long enough.
Please return at once.
You came all the way
from Camelot to scold me?
An immediate full-scale
confrontation is not advisable, sir.
As I believe you are well aware.
Indeed.
Dalflare, Benwick, and the Fairy King's Forest.
I can sense extremely hostile intent
from three different directions.
If something were to happen to you, what would
happen to those who call Camelot their home?
What a sly turn of phrase.
Could I not say the same to you?
It truly exists?!
Take me to Camelot with you!
Me too!
I want to go, too!
Are you crazy?! They're the ones
attacking your homeland!
True...
And who's protecting you?
Your nation's holy knights!
Ironside, what of the special mission I gave you?
Fear not, sir.
That matter is already on
its way to being settled.
You could have told me sooner.
Very well, let us retre—
M-My liege!
It's fine. Prepare to depart.
Meliodas, farewell for now.
Today has proven quite fruitful.
It's altered my view on many things.
Until now, you Knights of the Apocalypse
were to be a diversion to
spice up my tiresome days.
But this day marks a change in that course.
I will hereby hunt down every last one of the
Four Knights of the Apocalypse and their allies,
and exterminate them.
Fwah-hwa-wah!
I never thought we'd be able to
use the guest room in the castle.
How long has it been since
we're able to rest in bed?
Shut up! Stop jumping on the bed!
Hey, I heard there's a bath in the basement!
Let's all go in together!
I'm not going in with you!
Just get off my bed already!
What's she getting all riled up for?
Something up?
The Holy Knights risked their
necks to protect the city,
but did you hear the citizens?
Take me to Camelot with you!
Me too!
I want to go, too!
It just annoys me, is all.
But I think I know how they feel, a little.
Huh? What do you mean?
I don't know if the Camelot that King
Arthur showed us was real or fake,
but I definitely saw Grampa there.
What do you think Camelot is really like?
Beats me.
King Arthur's pretty mysterious himself.
I couldn't do a thing.
I was so useless.
He was that strong an enemy?
"Strong" ain't the half of it.
You fought very bravely, Percival.
But everyone else was super strong!
Gawain, and Tristan,
but Meliodas and Lancelot were even stronger!
Huh?
M-M-Meliodas? You mean the king, Meliodas?!
Yeah.
The leader of Liones?!
The Captain of the Seven Deadly Sins?!
You met him?!
I did.
All we saw was a little boy smaller
that Prince Tristan, even.
But people called him "my liege" and all.
There's no way King Meliodas is a little kid!
Well, we'll find out tomorrow, won't we?
C'mon, let's all hit the baths.
You first.
You should join us, Nasiens!
Huh?! No, I... I'll go alone, too...
Yo, Percy.
How about the five of us get a bite to eat?
I'm coming in.
Okay, tomorrow, then.
Prepared to Part Ways